Just copy this code as about the next step
and go back to our glue console
and we click on jobs.
We'll now click on the script editor and start fresh.
Create script here.
We're gonna paste the script we just copied
and we wanna name this.
We're gonna go back to the VS. Code.
Copy the name, copy this right here.
Enter Now you gotta provide job details.
We'll go here, provide the role.
Now if you remember the previous job, it took about one hour
to load two years of data from raw to curated.
And now we're doing aggregations.
And aggregations are costly, they're expensive.
So for two years of data,
what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna choose more number
of workers to start with.
Okay, I wanna see how long it takes
and then later I can reduce the number of workers
as required, as defined by ESLE, right?
I mean, if the job takes about four hours
and if it is fine for me, if the business can wait
for four hours, it's absolutely fine.
So for now, we'll just start at five, take a look at
how long it takes, and to add some more context,
let's say the job is supposed to start at 10:00 PM
and even if it takes six hours by 4:00 AM in the morning,
it finishes and the report really
runs at 6:00 AM in the morning.
You, you're still able to meet the SLA right SLA is
to finish a job by 6:00 AM Your job is finishing
by 4:00 AM in the morning.
You get the point. The runtime is always
governed by the SLA.
You shouldn't unnecessarily tune it
because you aren't in it.
You have to spend more on by adding more number of workers
and doing other stuff.
As such. We'll just now come down and then just save it
and then simply run it and then go to runs here.
It shows running to get this run,
and uh, we'll see you in the next video.